https://www.troemner.com/privacy-policy/

Call us at +1-800-352-7705 (M-F, 7:00 am - 3:30 pm EST)
My Cart (0)
Close
Recently added item(s)
There are no items in your shopping cart.
Calibration WeightsAnalytical Precision Weights
1 kg Analytical UltraClass Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
100 g Analytical UltraClass Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
100 g-1 mg Analytical UltraClass Weight Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
200 g-1 mg Analytical UltraClass Weight Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
OIML Precision Weights
100 g OIML Class E1 Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
1 kg OIML Class E1 Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
100 g-1 mg OIML Class E1 Weight Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
200 g-1 mg OIML Class E1 Weight Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Microgram Precision Weights
0.1 mg Sub-Milligram Analytical Class 0 Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
0.5 mg Sub-Milligram OIML Precision Class E1 Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
0.5 mg-0.05 mg Sub-Milligram UltraClass Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Cal-Paks
2 g-1 mg Analytical UltraClass Cal-Pak with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
100 g-20 mg Analytical Class 1 Cal-Pak with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
200 g-2 g Analytical Class 1 Cal-Pak with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
50 g-2 g Analytical Class 1 Cal-Pak with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Electronic Balance Weights
10 g Electronic Balance UltraClass Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
500 g Electronic Balance UltraClass Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
3 kg Electronic Balance UltraClass Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
5 kg Electronic Balance UltraClass Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Heavy Capacity Weights
100 lb Heavy Capacity Class 4 Weigh twith NVLAP Accredited Certificate
1000 lb Heavy Capacity Class 4 Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
50 kg Heavy Capacity Class 4 Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
500 kg Heavy Capacity Class 4 Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Stainless Steel Test Weights
2 lb Class F Test Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
1000 g Class F Test Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
2000 g-1 mg Test Weight Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
5000 g-1 mg Test Weight Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Cast Iron Test Weights
25 lb Class F Cast Iron Grip Handle Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
50 lb Class F Cast Iron Grip Handle Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
25 kg Class F Cast Iron Grip Handle Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
50 kg Class F Cast Iron Grip Handle Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Stainless Steel Slotted Weights
20 lb Class F Slotted Interlocking Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
10 lb Class F Slotted Interlocking Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
10 kg Class F Slotted Interlocking Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
2 kg Class F Slotted Interlocking Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Stainless Steel Hook Weights
1 lb Stainless Steel Hook Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
4 oz Stainless Steel Hook Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
1 kg Class F Stainless Steel Hook Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
200 g Class F Stainless Steel Hook Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Economical Stainless Steel Weights
100 g Stainless Steel Cylindrical Weight with Traceable Certificate
1000 g Stainless Steel Hook Weight with Traceable Certificate
1000 g-10 g Stainless Steel Hook Weight Set with Traceable Certificate
500 g-1 g Stainless Steel Weight Set with Traceable Certificate
Complete Accessory Kit
Polycarbonate Case for 500 g - 1 mg OIML Precision Weight Set
Polycarbonate Case for 500 g - 1 mg Analytical Precision Weight Set
Tolerance Charts | Uncertainty Charts | Certificate Options
1 kg Analytical UltraClass Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
100 g-1 mg OIML Class E1 Weight Set with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
200 g-2 g Analytical Class 1 Cal-Pak with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
25 lb Class F Cast Iron Grip Handle Weight with NVLAP Accredited Certificate
Calibration ServicesWeight CalibrationPipette CalibrationTemperature CalibrationPressure CalibrationHumidity CalibrationThermal Mass Flow CalibrationElectrical CalibrationDimensional CalibrationTime & Frequency CalibrationDew PointCalibration Devices by ServiceLab EquipmentShakers
Shaker, Heavy Duty, SHHD1619DG, US, 120V
Shaker, Extreme, SHEX1619DG, US, 120V
Shaker, Reciprocating, SHRC0719DG, US, 120V
Shaker, Rocking, SHRK04DG, US, 120V
Dry Block Heaters
Shaker, Heavy Duty, SHHD1619DG, US, 120V
Dry Block Heater, Heat Lid, HB2DGHL, US, 120V
Dry Block Heater, 4 Block, HB4DG, US, 120V
Airejector
Check Out Our NEW Analog Rocker!
Learn More About
Safety Certifications | Custom Manufacturing | Thermal Shake Touch
Shaker, Heavy Duty, SHHD1619DG, US, 120V
Shaker, Heavy Duty, SHHD1619DG, US, 120V
Vortex Mixer, Mini Analog, VXMNAL, US, 120V
Hotplate-Stirrer, Mini, HSMNHS4CAL, US, 120V
Reference CenterAbout TroemnerFrequently Asked QuestionsWeightsLab EquipmentCalibration ServicesCareers
Home
»
Troemner Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
We Protect Your Right to Privacy
Troemner.com respects your privacy. Our guidelines for protecting the information you provide us during your visit to our web site appear below.
Privacy Statement
This statement discloses the privacy practices for www.troemner.com. We have designed troemner.com so that no personal identifying information is displayed online or is accessible to the general public. You can browse the Troemner’s web site without telling us who you are or revealing any information about yourself.
Use of Data
For customer communication and marketing analysis we collect only the following information about our users: name, street address, zip code, state, and country and email address. We do not sell or distribute that information to any third party. We do not reveal your email address or other personal information.
Use of Your Email
When you provide us with your email address, we will occasionally send you email with recommendations or notices of new products, prices, and services. You have the option to be removed from this list at any time, simply by following the instructions at the bottom of the email.
Links
Troemner.com contains links to other web sites. Please note that when you click on one of these links, you are 'clicking' to another web site. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of these linked sites, as their privacy policies may differ from ours.
Log Files
Troemner.com maintains log files of the traffic that visits the troemner.com site. We do not link any information gathered in these log files to personally identifying information. Log files are used to manage traffic loads and information technology requirements for providing reliable service. Information collected includes IP addresses and browser types.
Feedback
We collect user feedback. Users who would like a response to specific questions concerning the service or their subscriptions are directed to the customer service area. These questions will be addressed as quickly as possible. We read all of our customer service queries and use the information contained therein only to resolve the question at hand.
Information security
All information gathered on the troemner.com site is stored and maintained in secure facilities that limit access to authorized personnel only. Our personnel can only access the information through a series of access-control procedures. Troemner employees are briefed about the company's privacy and security policies on a regular basis.
Contact Us
+1-800-352-7705
201 Wolf Drive • Thorofare, NJ 08086
M-F, 7:00am - 3:30pm EST
Contact Us
fbbloggertwitteryoutubelinkedin
Order Information
Returns Information
